https://www.ukopticalplastics.com/privacy-policy/

Search for:
Home (we are open for new enquiries despite the coronavirus . We are adopting the government’s social isolaton rules and advise all do the same and take great care to protect the NHS and our loved ones)
Our Skills
Optical Design
Opto-Mech Design
P.I.R. Fresnels
LED Lighting/Luminaires
Laser Scanners
Project Highlights
Tooling And Moulding
FAQ
Contact Us
Home (we are open for new enquiries despite the coronavirus . We are adopting the government’s social isolaton rules and advise all do the same and take great care to protect the NHS and our loved ones)
Our Skills
Optical Design
Opto-Mech Design
P.I.R. Fresnels
LED Lighting/Luminaires
Laser Scanners
Project Highlights
Tooling And Moulding
FAQ
Contact Us
EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Value the individual’s personal data supplied to us and make
sure we demonstrate trust and consideration.
Comply with the law when it comes to management of personal
information and undertake to guarantee moral standards.
Study and address the privacy of individuals when holding
personal information in an appropriate manner when updating any new systems
within UK Optical Plastics Ltd.
Be clear with persons about how we use their information and
how it was obtained.
Persons can update their personal data at any time by email
or written confirmation to UK Optical Plastics Ltd.
Persons can ask for their data to be removed at any time
from our organisation by email or written authorisation to UK Optical Plastics
Ltd.
To retain personal information to the minimum legal
requirement with a facility to remove when no longer required.
Any individual’s personal data will not be traded to a third
party for advertising, marketing, promotion or for any other reason.
Current protections updated to facilitate personal
information is kept safe.
To ensure suitable assets in place for looking after
personal details.
Frequently inspect our system for updates required.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy Policy
